What is your favorite book?
My favorite book is Nabokov's «Lolita».
Nabokov is my favorite writer.  
Have you read his other books?
Yes, I read all of his books.
What is your favorite movie?
My favorite movie is  «Titanic».
What music do you like?
I like different kinds of music.
What is your favorite band?
My favorite group is The Beatles.
What cuisines do you like?
I like different cuisines.
For example, I like Italian, Japanese, Chinese cuisines.
Is Chinese cuisine similar to Japanese?
Yes, it is similar.


Alessia what will you this evening?
Today evening I will read a book at home.  And you?
I will be work on a project.
What will you be doing tomorrow?
I don't have plans.
Why don't you have plans with John?
He is busy.
Do you like John?
Yes, but I think he likes Sofia.
Who is Sofia?
She is his colleague.
She is a Chinese engineer.
Really?
I need a new engineer.
Give me her telephone number.
OK.
Why do you think John likes Sofia?
Because she is beautiful and intelligent.


You seem sad, John.
Yes, I am sad.
Why?
I love Ezgi, but she has a boyfriend.
Who is her boyfriend?
His name is Hakan.
He is a businessman.
He is rich.
But that is not important.
I think that Ezgi wants a sensitive man.
You're right.
I agree.
But Hakan is very pleasant and funny.
And he loves to dance.
Ah!  Then you have a problem.
When Hakan was a student,
 he created an internet company.
Very interesting.


Hello!
Are you the new candidate?  Sofia?
Hello!  Yes, I am Sofia.
What's your name? (formal)
Good.  My name is Marcel.
Pleased to meet you.
Sorry that I am late.
The bus was late.
No problem!
Please, sit down. (formal)
Thank you.
Where are you from?
I am from Mexico.
Why do you want to work in Italy?
Because I like Italian culture.
Is it your first time in Italy?
No, I was in Italy four years ago.
Where were you in Italy?
I was in Milan.
Which city is bigger, Milan or Rome?
Rome is bigger.
There are more people here I like Rome more.
Where are there more tourists?  En Paris ou en Toulouse?
In Rome.


Is Italian a difficult language?
Yes, Italian is a very difficult language.
Which language is more difficult?
English or Italian?
Italian is more difficult.
English is easier than Italian.
How long have you been studying Italian?'
Three years.
You speak very well!
Do you go to class every day?
Yes, from Monday to Friday.
Thank you, I will take you for the job.


How was your first working week?
Everything all right?
Everything all right.
You seem tired.
Yes, I am a little tired.
Do you want to get dinner with me?
Yes, of course.
Are you hungry?

Can I buy you a drink?
OK, thanks.
What do you want?
I will take a beer.
I would like some wine.


Alessia, you seem pensive.
What are you thinking about?
John wants to read some books in Italian,
so I want to give him my books.
Which books will you give him?
I still don't know.
I will go home to look for some good books.
Will you have vacations next week?
Yes.
Do you have plans for the vacation?
Yes, I will go to the sea.
With who?
With John.
Where will you go, exactly?
To Normandy.


Who can tell me how to say birthday in French?
John, do you remember?
No, I don't remember.
I forgot.
Anniversaire
Can I go to the toilet?
Yes, but during the pause.
When is the pause?
In five minutes.
What is the difference between toilet and salle de bain?
In the salle de baine, there is a bath tub.


John, let's talk about the future.
Are children important to you?
Yes.  I want to have children.
How many?
I would like to have four children.
Two boys and two girls.
And you?
I want to have three children.
Where will we live?
Will we live in France or in America?
I want to live in France.
I want to live here, in Paris.
Perfect!
Do you want to get a dog?
Yes!


Sofia!
Maryanna!
Where are you going?
I'm going to the store.
I want to buy new clothes.
A where are you going?
I'm going home.
I did some shopping at the supermarket.
I need to cook dinner.
I'm having dinner with Marcel this evening.
I heard that you are dating Marcel.
That's very interesting!
Yes, it's true.
I want you to tell me about it.
Are you in a hurry?
Yes, unfortunately, I'm in a hurry.
Can we meet over the weekend?
We can get a coffee.
Yes.  We can have lunch together Saturday or Sunday.
I will be busy Saturday.
But on Sunday I'm free.
Then until the meeting on Sunday (saying goodbye).
I have important news!
Yes?  What kind of news?
John and I are getting married.
Congratulations!
When will the wedding be?
The wedding will be next year.
















